



320 Memorial Dr. Cambridge, MA 02139

Cell: 801-682-0009 camillew@mit.edu

PROFILE

As a sophomore at MIT, I am enjoying a rigorous curriculum pursuing a Bachelor of Science degree in Chemical Engineering. I have a perfect 5.0 GPA, and look forward to spending the upcoming summer enriching my experience in the field of Chemical Engineering through practical application of my technical knowledge.

AWARDS

U.S. PRESIDENTIAL SCHOLAR 2009

--US DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION, STATE OF UTAH REPRESENTATIVE, WASHINGTON, D.C

NATIONAL MERIT SCHOLAR FINALIST —2009

MATHEMATICS STERLING SCHOLAR, NORTHRIDGE HIGH SCHOOL, LAYTON, UT -2009

PERFECT 4.0 GPA AND HONOR ROLL —2003-2009

COCA-COLA SCHOLARS PROGRAM SEMIFINALIST -2009

CLASS VALEDICTORIAN—2006

SCIENCE DEPARTMENTAL AWARD/STUDENT OF THE YEAR—2006

NASA SCIENCE APPLICATION ARTICLE AWARD -2005

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH INTERNSHIP, UNIVERSITY OF UTAH, SALT LAKE CITY, UT— SUMMER 2010

Ran a series of CO2 sequestration experiments at high temperature and pressure, using spent shale, brine, and CO2.

EVENT STAFF, MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, CAMBRIDGE, MA - 2010

Part-time employment. Responsibilities: working to help events run smoothly, mainly sports-related responsibilities (scorekeeping, line judging, etc.).

SUMMER CHEMISTRY 1060, UNIVERSITY OF UTAH, SALT LAKE CITY, UTAH — SUMMER 2008

Labs and Lectures, June 10-July 19, received an A in the class.

LIFEGUARD AND WATER SAFETY INSTRUCTOR, CLEARFIELD AQUATIC CENTER, CLEARFIELD, UT -2007-2009, SUMMER 2010

NATIONAL HONOR SOCIETY MEMBER (VICE PRES. FOR TWO YEARS) — 2004-2009

VOLUNTEER TUTOR, LINCOLN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, LAYTON, UT —2008-2009

VOLUNTEER ENGLISH LANGUAGE TUTOR, JAPANESE AND HISPANIC NEIGHBORHOOD FAMILIES, LAYTON, UTAH — 2006-2008

Used various resources to plan English language lessons. Lessons for the Japanese family were taught in Japanese and English; Lessons for native Spanish speakers were taught in English.

FLUENT IN SPOKEN JAPANESE, LIVED IN JAPAN FOR 6 YRS — 1992-1996, 1999-2001

SPANISH I & II, NORTHRIDGE HIGH SCHOOL, LAYTON, UT — 2006-2008

EDUCATION

Massachusetts Institute of Technology — GPA: 5.0, Chemical Engineering, 2013

Northridge High School — GPA: 4.0, Class Rank: 1 out of 620

TECHNICAL CLASSES TAKEN/CURRENT CLASSES

Fall 2010: Thermodynamics and Kinetics, Differential Equations, Organic Laboratory Chemistry

Spring 2010: Physics 2 (Electricity 7 Magnetism), Introduction to Chemical Engineering, Organic Chemistry

Fall 2009: Physics 1 (Mechanics), Multivariable Calculus, Advanced Freshman Chemistry

HOBBIES

Running, reading, singing, and learning new things.

REFERRALS

Personal: Rotciv Harris, Neighbor, Young Women's Leader, babysitting employer; Phone: 801-444-4370

Work: Aaron Udy, Supervisor (Clearfield Aquatic Center), Phone: 801-774-9620

Donna Russell, Aquatic Director (Clearfield Aquatic Center), Phone: 801-776-9375